Hold on tight.
Gabby's Dollhouse: The Movie is a family, comedy,
adventure film directed by Ryan Crego.
Gabby heads out on a road trip with her Grandma Gigi to
the urban wonderland of Cat Francisco.
But when Gabby's dollhouse, her most prized possession, ends up in the hands of an eccentric cat lady named Vera, Gabby sets off on
an adventure through the real world to get the Gabby Cats back together and save the dollhouse before it's too late.
Gabby, played by Laila Lockhart Kraner.
Grandma Gigi, played by Gloria Estefan.
Vera, played by Kristen Wiig.
Pandy Paws (voice), played by Logan Bailey.
Daniel James 'DJ' Catnip (voice), played by Eduardo Franco.
Cakey (voice), played by Juliet Donenfeld.
Gabby's Dollhouse: The Movie is a 2025 American live-action animated musical fantasy comedy film based on the Netflix series Gabby's
Dollhouse, which was created by Traci Paige Johnson and Jennifer Twomey, both of whom serve as executive producers.
Produced by DreamWorks Animation, the film was directed by Ryan Crego from a screenplay by the writing teams of Mike Lew
and Rehana Lew Mirza, and Adam Wilson and Melanie Wilson LaBracio, based on a story conceived by Crego.
Combining live-action and animation, it stars Laila Lockhart Kraner, who reprises her role from the
series with Jason Mantzoukas, Gloria Estefan, and Kristen Wiig joining the cast.
The plot follows Gabby as she goes on a road trip with her grandmother to the urban wonderland of Cat
Francisco and embarks on an adventure to save her dollhouse and the Gabby Cats from a cat lady.
DreamWorks Animation announced a feature-length film based on Gabby's Dollhouse in April 2024,
with Crego and Steven Schweickart attached as director and producer, respectively.
It was also announced that same month that Kraner
set to reprise her role as Gabby.
Filming began in July 2024 in Vancouver, British Columbia, with
further casting running from February to May 2025.
It is the second live-action DreamWorks Animation film, following the 2025 remake of How to Train Your
Dragon (2010), as well as DreamWorks Animation's first live-action film that is not a remake.
Gabby's Dollhouse: The Movie premiered in Melbourne on September 13, 2025, and was
released by Universal Pictures in the United States on September 26, 2025.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics
and has grossed $80.3 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of friendship, magic, cat, mermaid, musical.
The tone is lighthearted.